<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CatsQuiz</string>
    <string name="true_button">TRUE</string>
    <string name="false_button">FALSE</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="prev_button">Prev</string>
    <string name="answer_is">The answer is</string>
    <string name="cheat_button">Cheat</string>
    <string name="warning_text">Are you sure you want to do this?</string>
    <string name="show_answer_button">Show answer</string>
    <string name="judgment_toast">Cheating is wrong.</string>
    <string name="correct_string">Correct</string>
    <string name="incorrect_string">Incorrect</string>
    <string name="cheated_string">Cheated</string>
    <string name="share_menu_item">Share</string>
    <string name="share_result_string">Share Result</string>
    <string name="score_string">Score</string>
    <string name="quiz_result_msg">Quiz result</string>

    <!-- Questions -->
    <string name="question_whiskers_hunt">A cat\'s whiskers help it hunt at night.</string>
    <string name="question_heart_beat">When resting, a cat\'s heart beats nearly twice as fast as a human\'s.</string>
    <string name="question_see_in_darkness">A cat can see in complete darkness.</string>
    <string name="question_jump_high">A cat can jump up to 5 times its own height.</string>
    <string name="question_drink_saltwater">Cats can drink saltwater.</string>
    <string name="question_cat_breeds">There are 500 breeds of cats.</string>
    <string name="question_paw_sweat">Cats only sweat through their paws.</string>
    <string name="question_first_space_cat">On 18 October 1963, Félicette was the first cat to travel into space.</string>
    <string name="question_more_domestic_dogs">There are more dogs as pets in the world than cats.</string>
    <string name="question_egyptian_cats">Over 5000 years ago, the Egyptians considered cats to be evil.</string>
    <string name="question_toxic_chocolate">Like dogs, cats can become ill or even die because of eating chocolate.</string>
    <string name="question_boarding_ships">In the 15th century, due to superstitions, cats were forbidden from boarding ships.</string>
    <string name="question_oldest_cats_breed">The Egyptian Mau is probably the oldest breed of cat.</string>
    <string name="question_meow_communication">Cats rarely meow to communicate amongst themselves.</string>
    <string name="question_colors_spectrum">Cats see a broad spectrum of colors.</string>
    <string name="question_distance_near_vision">Cats have blurred distance vision and poor near vision.</string>
    <string name="question_cats_dream">Cats dream.</string>
    <string name="question_deep_purring">Deep purring can be a sign of well-being but also a sign of pain.</string>
    <string name="question_smallest_breed">The smallest breed of cat is the Singapura.</string>
    <string name="question_refined_palate">Cats have a refined palate.</string>
    <string name="question_paw_pads">The pads on a cat\'s paw don\'t feel anything.</string>
    <string name="question_head_rubbing">A cat rubs its head on people to "mark" its smell.</string>
    <string name="question_domesticated_cats">Cats are more domesticated than dogs.</string>
    <string name="question_turkish_van_cats">Turkish Van cats like water.</string>
    <string name="question_hear_better_than_humans">Cats can hear three times better than humans.</string>
    <string name="question_speed_run">A cat can run at a speed of 31 mph (49 km/h).</string>
    <string name="question_fewer_bones">Cats have fewer bones than humans.</string>
    <string name="question_see_below_nose">Cats cannot see the area below their nose.</string>
    <string name="question_sense_of_smell">A cat\'s sense of smell is not as good as a human\'s.</string>
    <string name="question_ear_muscles">Cats have 32 muscles in each ear. Humans only have 6.</string>
    <string name="question_taste_sugar">Cats can\'t taste sugar.</string>
    <string name="question_hot_food">Cats prefer hot food.</string>
    <string name="question_awake_life">In total, a cat spends 4 years of its life awake.</string>
    <string name="question_collarbones">Cats do not have collarbones.</string>
    <!-- contents from http://quipoquiz.com/quiz/cats -->
    <!-- Answers -->
    <string name="answer_whiskers_hunt">A cat\'s whiskers detects movements of air. This allows them to detect anything moving in the dark.</string>
    <string name="answer_heart_beat">When resting, a cat\'s heart beats at 110 to 140 beats per minute.</string>
    <string name="answer_see_in_darkness">Even though cats can see in the dark, they cannot see in complete darkness. They need a small source of light in order to see.</string>
    <string name="answer_jump_high">In one leap, a cat can jump up to 5 times its own height.</string>
    <string name="answer_drink_saltwater">A cat\'s kidneys can filter sea salt. This allows them to rehydrate by drinking seawater.</string>
    <string name="answer_cat_breeds">There are around 80 breeds of cats. This number is poorly defined because cat breeds are not uniformly named or recognized, or their standards are sometimes different according to cat association in every country.</string>
    <string name="answer_paw_sweat">Cats only have sweat glands between the pads of their paws.</string>
    <string name="answer_first_space_cat">Félicette was the first cat to travel into space. She was also the only cat to survive a space mission.</string>
    <string name="answer_more_domestic_dogs">In the world, there are around 600 million domestic cats and around 500 million domestic dogs.</string>
    <string name="answer_egyptian_cats">The Egyptians did not consider cats evil: on the contrary, they worshiped cats. When domestic cats died, they were often embalmed.</string>
    <string name="answer_toxic_chocolate">Theobromine, a substance present in chocolate, is toxic to dogs and cats.</string>
    <string name="answer_boarding_ships">In the 15th century, almost all ships had cats. Their role was to exterminate any rats on board.</string>
    <string name="answer_oldest_cats_breed">The Egyptian Mau is probably the oldest breed of cat. In fact, "mau" means cat in Egyptian.</string>
    <string name="answer_meow_communication">With a few exceptions, cats only meow for communicating with humans. When cats communicate with other cats they use grunts, growls, howls, whistles, cries, etc.</string>
    <string name="answer_colors_spectrum">Cats see a very limited range of colors. They see yellow and blue but not red.</string>
    <string name="answer_distance_near_vision">Cats have blurred distance vision and poor near vision. Their vision is best between 4 and 32 in. (10 and 80 cm).</string>
    <string name="answer_cats_dream">Cats dream from when they are a week old. When sleeping, cats have similar brain waves to those of humans.</string>
    <string name="answer_deep_purring">Purring is often a sign of well-being, but a cat may also purr when it is stressed or when it is in pain.</string>
    <string name="answer_smallest_breed">The smallest breed of cat is Singapura, which weighs only around 4 lb. (1.8 kg).</string>
    <string name="answer_refined_palate">A cat\'s sense of taste is less developed than that of a human. Cats have fewer than 500 taste buds while humans have over 9000.</string>
    <string name="answer_paw_pads">The pads are covered in highly sensitive touch receptors that allow the cat to evaluate the texture, temperature and resistance of a surface, object, or prey.</string>
    <string name="answer_head_rubbing">Cats have scent glands around their lips, under their chin, and between their eyes and ears. Therefore, they mark their smell on objects and people with their heads.</string>
    <string name="answer_domesticated_cats">Present day cats are a lot closer to their wild ancestors than dogs are. They are therefore less domesticated than dogs.</string>
    <string name="answer_turkish_van_cats">Unlike most cats, Turkish Van cats like water and will go swimming to cool off.</string>
    <string name="answer_hear_better_than_humans">The range of sound vibrations detected by cats is around 3 times wider than that detected by humans.</string>
    <string name="answer_speed_run">A cat can run at 31 mph (49 km/h), but only over a short distance.</string>
    <string name="answer_fewer_bones">Cats have at least 24 more bones than humans. While humans have 206 bones, cats have at least 230. This number varies because the number of vertebrae in the tail changes from one breed of cat to another.</string>
    <string name="answer_sense_of_smell">Thanks to hundreds of millions of olfactory sensors that line its nasal cavity, a cat\'s sense of smell is 100 times more sensitive to smell than a human\'s. </string>
    <string name="answer_ear_muscles">With their 32 muscles in each ear, cats can rotate their ears independently and so they are able to detect sounds better.</string>
    <string name="answer_taste_sugar">Cats do not have the necessary receptors to taste sugars. You can\'t coax them with sweet things!</string>
    <string name="answer_hot_food">Cats prefer their food to be at room temperature, not too cold and not too hot.</string>
    <string name="answer_awake_life">On average, a cat sleeps for 2/3 of a day. At the end of its life, an average cat will have slept 8 years and been awake for 4.</string>
    <string name="answer_collarbones">Cats do not have collarbones, which allows them to squeeze into small spaces. If a cat can get its head through an opening, then the rest of its body will also be able to squeeze through.</string>
    <!-- contents from http://quipoquiz.com/quiz/cats -->
</resources>